Logan Reynolds - Software Engineer SF, CA - (415) 886-0145 - LoganReynoldsLWR@gmail.com

Passionate full-stack software engineer, having studied at three book camps, two colleges & with a lot of self-study. Having worked on many projects in teams & on his own has the necessary experience to accomplish the job.

EXPERIENCE

Dance4Healing.com — Full-Stack Software Engineering Intern — 2020 - PRESENT

 Work experience with AI, Express.js, Heroku, Node.js, Jade, Mongoose.js, Twilio, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Passport.js, Vimeo JS Player SDK, Bit Bucket, Git, Github, Browserify & more.

Craigslist & More — Freelancing in Web & App Development — 2019 - PRESENT

Worked on the development of application, websites & more for clients seeking a Web Design, Software Engineering, or UI/UX Design contractor.

Amazon.com — Independent Content Creator — 2018 - PRESENT

• Orchestrated the publication of 10+ ebooks on Amazon including paper & Audible publication of books.

EDUCATION

Make School "Dominican University", San Francisco — CS Bachelor's Degree — 2022

- Bachelor's degree in applied computer science at Make School Accredited through Dominican University.
- Concentrations include but are not limited to mobile development, web development (full stack) & data science/machine learning.
- Languages & frameworks include but are not limited to Python, JavaScript, Swift, Go, Flask, Django, Node.js, React.js, UIKit, CoreData, Foundation, NumPy, Pandas, Scikit-Learn, Keras & TensorFlow.

Meda — Full-Stack Bootcamp — 2020 - PRESENT

• Full-stack projects using HTML, CSS, Git & GitHub, JavaScript, Node.js, jQuery & more.

Code Tenderloin, San Francisco — Coding Bootcamp — 2019

Participated in an intensive 6-week program to develop skills in HTML, CSS, Javascript & completed over 90 assignments to hone front end web
development skills.

Noisebridge, San Francisco — Programming Classes — 2019

Studied Python, C# & Unity at Noisebridge.

Code The Dream, www.codethedream.org — Coding Bootcamp — 2019

• Completing an online course in Ruby, Rails, ERB, Active Record, AWS, HTML, CSS & SQL.

Online Learning — Software Engineering |UI/UX Design Classes — 2014

 Online courses with Linda "Linked In Learning," Hacker Rank, CodePen.io, Team Treehouse, Code Cademy, GitHub Learning Lab, Khan Academy, Udacity & so much more.

DVC, PleasantHill, CA — College — 2014

Classes in Business, Art Drawing, UI/UX Design, HTML, Dreamweaver, & Photoshop (intro & advanced).

SKILLS

- Javascript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, React.js, Express.js, Terminal, Pug, Git, GitHub, BitBucket, Bootstrap, NPM, AWS, Adobe Creative Suite, CI/CD, WordPress & more.
- 10+ yrs expertise in creative tools to include Adobe suite (e.g., Photoshop) & Sketch.

SAMPLE WORK

- Software Engineer Portfolio Website LWRGitHub.GitHub.io
- Full-Stack Software Engineering intern dance4healing.com
- GitHub github.com/LWRGitHub
- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/logan-reynolds
- eBook covers, UX/UI Design

https://www.amazon.com/s?i=digital-text&rh=p_27%3AThe+Midnight+Dream+Publishing&s=relevancerank&text=The+Midnight+Dream+Publishing&ref=dp_byline_sr_ebooks_1